I am Luca Lazzari, I am responsible for the production and clothing of Ita Imperia.
Imperia is a leading company in fast fashion. The main feature is production
in a short time. From the creation of the stylist to the delivery of the finished product,
only seven days pass on average. The continuous search for innovation by the
owner has allowed us to develop increasingly complex and increasingly advanced
technology systems. We have seen several 3D solutions, but CLAW has struck us for its
ease of use and for the possibility of creating the entire chain, from the commercial to the style
to the modeling. Depending on the departments in which CLAW 3D has been used, we immediately had
satisfactory results within a few months. The CLAW 3D program has allowed us to take
decisions much more quickly and with a much lower margin of error.
I am Angelo Mastri, a male and female modeler at Imperial. I started my work in 1985,
when it was still handmade and the models were made on cardboard. I arrived at
Imperial at the end of 2016 and on that occasion I saw for the first time the 3D position of CLAW.
We immediately started working on the 3D project, with unexpected results for me from the
first few weeks. Today, at Ufficio Modelli, we have three CLAW CAD positions. We work
in close contact with stylists. By using the 2D part of the CLAW system, we are able
to modify volumes, lengths, and details in real time. Everything that was previously
done manually, we can do it on 3D. In summary, we have significantly shortened
the design times by optimizing the final result and practically reducing the error
to zero. The future is in the hands of 3D technology.